so i have a little bit of time this morning so i just wanted to take it to expose a colonizer
so this white man corey sam can is in the comments in several spaces but i just took one for you
saying maybe if she had complied with the ice agent's orders to get out of her car she would
still be alive today let's take a look at corey sam can now mind you people in the comments because
he posted this are like how about you take me out of this because you literally reached out to try
to sell me something that i didn't inquire you to what can i say black women love me hashtag black
girl magic look at the person can you remove my chat from these shenanigans so these are the
individuals who are not bots this is a real white man who decided that he would wake up
from his slumber of corniness to then disparage a woman who was out there alerting folks to the
presence of ice black women do not love you how much did you pay these ladies
they better got some good bread